Hello friends welcome back to my school
essay deposit interest interpress so today
in this video we will see the road and
learn about some running staff so
if you also do not want to miss the details
then definitely watch this video till the end
so let's start first of all
if we look at yesterday doctor
and 3000 and s&p 500 silver at 4163 level
and below 3006 solid west indies is above 4800
in the cash market we still have edison
electronics after this if we look at
here that means when we can see around 4000 134
here the market is above 30
so if we talk about a consolidation phase in this then
CR is coming here that
in its four to five hours you will see an option
here comes down profit after
tax
side 21.90 here you can see the
premium here compared to last year and
Shyam stock so in this board meeting it has been
decided to go digital and for this
question  You can get up to 360 feet in this,
because of this business, a
little bit more bank details were updated in it, it has been
decided to raise a fund from the market here through securities, keeping
this in mind, in the next few days we will get a
little bit more information on this topic from the Special Economic
Zone, they have left side
investment company 100 and in the shares of this area,
Tata Steel Products, Jin-Jin
Network, Oct 8th
teacher, you for jo laptop soon, if we talk about this time, then
even today you can see a little bit of it here in Jubilant for a case
because the company has
developed an oral communication skill of Remedy here, so if
this production on commercial specific, then there will be a
little bit of upset in the stock in future also, if
you liked this video then like and subscribe to the channel
and if you want here, till then see you
in the next video, thank you.